Gold Grotter, the King of the Pirates,
attained every treasure
that the world had to offer.
Smiling, even as he stood upon the scaffold,
he issued a challenge to the world.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
Now those who dare to dream hoist their
flags and sail into the Great Pirate Era.
I don't know if you do
it, it's M .I .N .I .N .E.
Oh, the only reason i
am is with our rules.
No doubt, it's the only part of me.
I never have the same life.
I can't believe it,
it's the only way i can.
But the future is the same.
I can't believe it, it's the same.
We go!
We go! No!
Come on.
Just apologize already.
Don't you have something
you want to live for?
Well, kid, what you thinking?
You screwed up and now it's time to pay.
So speak up.
Please, take a look at that brat.
Obviously you scared him silent, Captain.
I can't blame the kid after
that guy with the schnoz
and that chick with the long
hair picked a fight with us.
We're in a worse mood than usual.
Now if you don't want to be our personal
punching bag, you'd best ask forgiveness!
Neil get down in the
dirt forget your pride.
Otherwise, you're gonna end up throwing
your life away over some small mistake.
After all our captain's trigger
figure can be a little twitchy.
Come on kid just do it
you shouldn't mess around
with Straw Hat luffy you're
gonna die if you don't.
Do what he says all
right look i'm sorry now
i got somewhere to be
what's wrong with you?
Bad move say goodbye punk.
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
What happened?
Hey, that guy.
Did he do something?
Why are you being such an ass about this?
I just want to go fish.
Well, too bad you can't.
Give me one good reason.
And while you're at it, give me one good
reason why I should even listen to you.
I don't want to hang out
together any more than you do,
but I can't let you get lost.
Don't get me wrong, though.
Nothing would make me happier
than leaving you here for good.
Too bad, huh?
The point is, everyone's
meeting on the ship,
so you don't get to go
fishing on your own.
What a joke.
Number seven thinks he can talk crap
to number one and get away with it.
You think you're better than me
just because you got here first?
It's not like everyone
swam to Sabaody, all right?
You got nothing to brag about!
Sure.
Whatever you say.
Number seven.
Fine!
You want to fight me?
I've trained these legs on the
shores of hell for two years!
Then you better use them to run,
because I will cut you in half!
Captain Luffy! Aw, man. You okay?
Luffy!
Oh my gosh, I missed you guys so much!
It's me!
Hey, Luffy!
Franky!
Nami!
Sniper Gang!
Awesome!
Oh wow, you sure changed
a lot in two years, huh?
I bet you're all super strong now!
What are the Straw Hats up to?
They're just sitting.
Did something happen?
Uh, yeah, but keep it down.
They're pissed off, so
don't look them in the eye.
You don't want to pick
a fight with these guys.
What the hell?
Whoa, what happened, boss?
I was messed up.
Like, all of a sudden, I got these chills.
Never seen a trick like that before.
Oh, I forgot.
But, we got another problem actually.
The thing is, Kaku, I mean
Robin, isn't a real pickle.
She was kidnapped and
you let the bastards go?
Yeah, sorry.
I mean it all happened so fast.
They must be human traffickers.
This could be real bad.
They could try to sell her at auction.
Like what happened with Kuma?
Uh, get a good look, Adam?
No, like I said, it
happened all sudden like.
Hey, Captain,
they must have nabbed Kaku because
they thought she was the real Robin.
We might be in over our heads here.
I should have known, you're right.
She does look just like the real thing.
Guess that worked against us this time.
Hey, are you keeping secrets from me?
I don't care. Leave her.
It's not our problem if she dies.
What?
Okay.
Are you nuts?
Luffy, Robin is our friend!
Listen, what is this thing?
And why does it talk?
If this is supposed to be
a joke, it's not funny!
We lost Robin once, don't care about that!
See, it's doing it again.
It can't be a toy.
Take it back, Luffy!
Get off of me!
Alright, screw this thing with Robin
and screw this stuffed animal thing!
We gotta get our whole team
together here on Crow 46!
And pronto!
That punk with the long nose,
that woman with the orange hair,
and that crappy kid
with the giant backpack!
Hunt them down and kick their asses!
We're gonna show the whole damn world what
happens when you cross-Straw Hat Luffy!
Uh, Roger!
Don't kill him yet so we can make
a good show of it, huh, Captain?
We'll drag him through the streets till
everyone on Sabo and he's shaking in fear!
Works for me!
Are you crazy?!
Cut it out!
It's only been two years.
What happened to you?
This is wrong.
I don't know. I'm just.
I'm so sad. Right?
Now you're making me cry.
For the last time.
What is this stupid thing?
And none of you want to help.
Robin.
Nobody's gonna say anything.
Why is this runt so attached to us anyway?
When we're done here.
Maybe we should try selling it.
Damn it.
Forget this.
I don't have time to argue with you.
I'll save her.
You're on my own!
I don't need you!
I'm coming, Robin!
Hold on!
What was that?
They have a fight?
I don't know.
But it's definitely them.
I mean, they haven't aged
well in the past two years.
But nobody else has a weird pet like that.
Looks like the reports are true after all.
They're alive.
The Straw Hats are back, and
they're causing trouble again.
This is Grove Number 47. It's them.
We've sighted six Straw
Hats and their pet.
The rumors that they recruited are
the pirates seem to be true as well.
They should be assembling on
Grove Number 46 any minute now.
Understood.
Then we'd better move quickly.
Evacuate the locals before
this becomes a war zone.
Roger.
Pirates are gathering at Grove 46.
Our targets are the Straw Hats.
We'll engage them in the Lawless Zone.
They may have reinforcements.
Block all routes of escape.
Close in on them from
Grove 40, 42, and 44.
Make it snappy.
G1 is sending in backup now.
Sent a matter, sir.
I'm heading in first.
Pucci and Pucci will accompany me.
Whoa!
You're deploying pacifistas, sir?
Of course I am!
You fools!
Haven't you learned not to
underestimate the Straw Hats?
It's been two years since the war.
Surely they've only grown
stronger during that time.
They may be rookies, but make no mistake,
they're the most dangerous pirates here!
As for what happened last time,
we were never able to determine why Kuma
sent them away instead
of apprehending them.
But even after his personality was wiped,
his actions seemed to indicate that
they would be returning here someday.
And now that they have, we must ensure
this doesn't end like it did two years ago.
Let's move!
To be
continued...
Sanji! Franky!
What happened to them? Why?
Robin gets taken away and you don't care?
What's wrong with you?
I've been working so hard these past
two years to be a better doctor!
But for what?
Chopper!
Hey!
Yoo-hoo, over here!
I can tell it was you from a mile away!
It's Yasopp!
Jeez, you got so big!
Just look at you!
I bet I could even ride
your back, couldn't I?
You doing okay?
Oh, so cuddly!
I'm sure the Lady
Reindeers just adore you!
I missed you, Chopper, so much!
Uh, uh, Nami?
Uh-huh.
Wait a second.
I'm happy to see you guys and all,
but now's not the time for this.
Robin is in serious trouble.
Huh?
They're just pretending to be you?
That's why there's two Nami's?
Use your head, okay?
Robin was able to avoid the
government for 20 years.
Do you really think someone could
just grab her and stuff her in a bag?
No offense, but come on.
I see, I have a tough time telling humans
apart, but she didn't even smell right.
Darn it, now I'm starting to get mad.
If we see one of them again, I'm gonna
punch them in their big fake face.
They've got some nerve,
pretending to be us.
I mean, why would they do
that in the first place?
It's almost like we're
celebrities or something.
That's crazy.
Hey, don't let it go to your head.
Although you aren't that far off,
since our captain worked up quite a
reputation for fighting in that war.
I have to come up with a cool autograph.
I've already got one.
Come on, you two.
We're famous criminals, not celebrities.
Topper, where'd you go?
Come back.
And he sucks that little
dude was a pet for real.
He, like, doubled the credibility.
Oh, my side hurts.
Are you nuts?
That talking stuffed animal thing
was part of the real Straw Hat,
so you let it get away?
Why didn't you tell me?
And why are you looking for it?
Oh, sure, go look for it like
we have any idea where we went.
Yeah, I mean, Sabo Odi is super
big, and that guy was teeny tiny.
I can't do this.
I am dying here!
Forget running. We'll walk.
Power walk.
Hancock was right.
With all the pirates around,
this mustache is pretty handy.
I don't want to fight
with those guys anyway.
Look, it's that kid with the backpack.
Maybe our luck ain't so bad after all.
Boss called him a kid, but he kind
of looks like an old man to me.
Oh, it's you guys?
Hey, friend, we need you to come with us!
Let's do this nice and quiet, okay?
We don't want any trouble You really
pissed off our captain, kiddo?
I'd prepare for the worst if I was you!
What's wrong?
You're so scared you can't even talk?
Hey, Sanji, how's it going?
And Zoro, too, wow!
Long time no see, huh, guys?
Too long, right?
Yeah, well, let's get going then.
You mean the rest of
the crew's here already?
Sorry I was so late.
Good thing you found me.
Well, he knows the Straw
Heads, but we don't know him.
Like I care.
Just take him to Luffy
and he'll sort this out.
Reporting from Grove 46.
All the new recruits the Straw
Hats picked up are gathering here.
And from the looks of things, I'd say
there might be nearly a hundred of them.
Most of them are nobodies, but
there are four captains at least.
I see Gashed Albion for one.
He's worth 92 million.
Then there's Libserviced Outta.
Who's worth 88 million.
But those aren't the ones
I'm really worried about.
They've also got wet-haired caribou.
Worth 210 million.
The captain of his crew.
He brought his brother with him.
Blood-splattered coribou.
His bounty's at 190 million.
The Navy is here?
So they know.
Very well, then. Take it easy! No pushing!
We're songs, okay?
And we're waiting for you!
I still need a moment more.
My fans are calling for an encore,
you see, and I can't let them down.
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
I think I owe them this much at
least, so please wait up for me.
Those cheese could bring a dead
man back from his grave, baby.
This is the Navy!
Nobody move!
What's the deal?
That's not cool.
This is the last living
member of the Rumbar Pirates.
The Humming Swordsman, Brook, presumed
dead until now with a bounty of 33 million.
Despite his skeletal state, our reports
indicate that Soul King is this pirate.
In addition to his previous crimes,
we have further information that indicates
he is now working for Straw Hat Luffy.
Soul King, Brook!
Or rather, Humming Swordsman, Brook!
You're under arrest for piracy!
No, it can't be true!
I feel like my whole life is a lie!
He was a pirate all along?
But wait, Stryhat Luffy's
been missing for years now.
It's been a good run,
Brook, but it's over.
Your betrayal's not exactly
a surprise, Mr. Manager.
You're the one to blame telling me you
were gonna retire right after the show.
How could you do this to me?
A pity,
but it seems like I would have been better
off keeping you in that cage after all.
We were gonna be rich, but
now our company's ruined.
You're nothing but a filthy traitor.
If my life's going to hell,
I'm taking you with me.
That is so cool!
Heck yeah!
Can I get a body like that too?
So can you like Transformers stuff,
shoot beams, missiles, laser eyes?
Hurry, show me, show me!
I can hear the dreams of men on
my massive metal shoulders. Wow!
I'm back and better than ever.
I'm not just me.
I've armored me, baby!
Robot! Robot!
I know he's cool, but stop
before you have a heart attack!
One thing's bugging me, though.
Those giant robo-hands
are great for bashing,
but how are you supposed
to do detail work?
Never doubt the master.
Whoa!
Dude!
He's got a hand in his hand!
Oh, my God!
Robin!
Nani!
I love the hair!
Wow, he looks terrible.
Did he do that to himself?
It's Franky, don't ask.
Whoa, this must be the coding, huh?
Wanna see something else cool?
Press my nose. Your nose?
Press and hold it for
three seconds or more.
Apply pressure to the nasal region, human.
Holy crap, he's like a real robot!
I'm excited.
One, two, three!
Wow, he grew hair!
Wait a sec, can you style it?
Easy as pie.
Hey, look who it is.
What's up?
Yeah, I see you.
Ugh, like our crew didn't
stick out enough already.
Can I see your new weapons, please? Can I?
Sorry buddy,
that's the main event, so we gotta
wait till the captain shows up, Mecha!
He made robot noises!
Is Mecha his new catchphrase?
Hello there!
Hey Rayleigh! Hey Chaka!
Sorry to interrupt your reunion,
but we've kinda got an incident.
Actually, two very large incidents
that demand your attention.
Put the guitar down now!
Hands in the air, pirate!
There's no escape!
Members of the band, my lovely
chorus, this will be my final song.
Will you share it with me?
Have no fear.
My music has more than just soul.
It has true power.
Are you insane?
You think anyone's gonna
let you play another song?
You might not see it this way, but I'm
grateful for the time we spent together.
Thank you for these past two years,
and thank you for bringing me here.
My crew and I have rather
tragic memories of this place.
We lost an important battle here last
time, but we're ready to start anew.
I'm the musician of the crew.
I may possess some
strength as a swordsman,
but my job is to make
our journey more fun.
I've heard the stories.
They think people are foolish enough
to believe that Straw Hat is dead.
Will you listen to me?
He's not!
Straw Hat Luffy is out
there, alive and kicking!
You can tell the world!
And while you're at it,
tell them he's going to be the
king of the pirates someday, too!
Boy, have I got some news for you guys!
We better print this one in a jiffy!
Yeah, baby, he's coming back
soon, and when he sets sail,
Well, I want to send
him off Soul King style!
That's so cool!
Do you love me down to my bones?
I'll dedicate this to
my crew, to my friends.
My soul will sing to you one last time!
Luffy, let's go to the new world together.
The show is over!
I said you're under arrest!
Would you shut up?
It's his last thought!
Let us hear it!
Please, what harm could it do?
She's right!
You can wait till the show
is over, you bastards!
Music is power.
Music is always on your side.
One, two, three, four.
I call this one New World.
This is Grove number 46 with an update.
The pirates keep pouring in.
There's definitely over a hundred.
Now none of the main
Straw Hats are here yet.
But even so, I would approach
with extreme caution.
This is bad.
Tell the backup they need to hurry.
Well now what have we here?
Who is this little fellow
whispering behind the rock?
Because he looks like a Navy soldier.
And my goodness what is this?
You weren't looking to crash
our harmless party, were you?
No! No!
That's not very civil at all!
Because if you were calling
your friends for backup,
that would not end well,
seeing as they weren't invited.
Show some manners.
I saw him.
He was calling. No!
I was going to call them, but I
hadn't gotten through them just yet.
That is good to hear.
And I say that for your sake, too.
Because if your friends did show up,
this grove would be covered in blood.
Their blood.
And your blood.
Come on, Caribou.
Back me up here. Huh?
I wasn't listening.
Who do you think you're bowing to, moron?
I'm over here.
Please forgive me.
You still can't get it right.
What, are you blind or just stupid?
He's famous for killing Marines.
Hmm? Hmm.
Ah, do you think this is a joke?
He really stabbed that guy.
Then the stories are true.
Gods, have mercy!
He is but a fool!
He grabbed his gun!
This poor misguided soul tried
to incite violence against me!
In your infinite kindness,
please show him mercy!
Sorry, gods. Sorry. Very sorry.
Sorry, gods.
Now, brother, bury him.
Bury this sinful transgressor alive.
I dig so that his poor soul may
be free. Roger! Dig it! Dig it!
Wait a second!
What if I call them and
tell them not to come?
That would be good, right?
That's enough, Caribou.
Huh?
You can bury that nobody later.
We got bigger fists to
fry right now. Yeah!
Just tell us what you want
from us, Captain Loopy!
We're ready to go!
Take a look around you, boys.
This is history in the making you
probably don't know each other yet.
But you'll be Titus brothers soon
enough from here on out your straw.
Not a bad deal and I swear
when I become King of the
Pirates you're gonna know
you made the right call!
But I need a promise from you first
cuz a real king needs loyal subjects
ones that will live and die for
him and wait on him hand and fight.
Anything you say you're the man who escaped
Impel Down wrecked Eni's lobby stormed?
Fruit Ford, and fought the Admirals!
You've got the world government
quaking in its boots!
Sailing the seas with you
is like a dream come true!
Listen,
there's only one man fit to be king of
the pirates and he's standing right there!
You get with him or you
get left in the dust!
Yeah!
Looks like the king's all here.
Is this it?
So where is everyone?
Stop making me wait!
All right, enough!
I didn't call you here at a party.
We got business to attend to.
Some jackasses out there haven't been
showing me the respect I deserve.
That is to say, they insulted my aunt.
A red-haired girl, a long-nosed
guy, and a brat with a backpack!
Find him and bring him to me!
The bastards are still in
the archipelago somewhere!
Consider it done, boss!
We'll make him suffer, you'll see!
I gotta say, though, people sure
can't change a lot in two years.
For one, you guys hardly
talk at all anymore.
He's more dangerous than we thought.
We gotta get him to the boss pronto
or he's gonna rat us out to air.
everyone.
Who is this guy?
I don't know, but in the meantime, let's
try not to talk so he doesn't catch on.
The captain's right there.
He can figure this
out on his own.
Sounds like a plan.
I don't know what happened,
but it seems like you're
getting along a lot better, too.
Yep.
Time changes lots of stuff.
Like your faces, I mean.
Unless you're wearing a disguise like me.
Still not saying anything?
The Navy? That's right.
They thought those fake Straw Hats were
the real deal and mobilized their forces.
Pacifistas, too.
I have them wiretapped, so
there's no mistaking it.
Anyway,
Brooke is finishing up his concert,
but I gave him a call backstage
to let him know what was going on.
He said he'd come after the
encore, so it shouldn't be long.
Oh yeah?
Giving up stardom to be a lowly pirate?
Goes without saying, but
the man's got a backbone.
All right, Nami.
Since you're the navigator,
there are a few tricks to operating
a coded ship I should pass on to you.
Uh, okay.
Sure, let's hear it.
We aren't getting ready
to take off, are we?
We're still missing half the crew here.
I mean, did Luffy even make
it to the archipelago yet?
It's all under control.
Captain! Huh?
I'm kind of in the middle
of something, you goons.
But we found a backpack
guy you was looking for.
That's good, right?
He's a friend of the crew, if you follow.
Hello, say hi.
In other words, Luffy
arrived earlier this morning.
It's almost time to go.
I gave Sanji a baby transponder
snail when he stopped by,
so I'll tell him to come back.
You should have Zoro with him, too.
Good.
We should hurry,
because any moment now, the Navy will
be attacking with a sizable force.
Unfortunately, there's no
way to contact your captain.
But if you follow this Vivre card,
you should be able to hunt him down.
Let's hope the fake straw
hats buy you a bit of time.
Grove 42 is on the outskirts,
so it's close to the sea.
Take the Sunny there and be ready
to depart on a moment's notice.
I'm sure you'd like to relax
after these two difficult years,
but it wasn't meant to be.
The winds of the new
world wait for no one.